Guide to the Thomas Day Thacher Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject files, 1919-1950; Series II; 17 linear feet (43 boxes)
  - Section A. Solicitor General
    - Solicitor General's staff resignations - correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 20, Folder 393)
    - Real Estate Bond Holders Reorganization Congressional Hearings Minutes, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 394)
    - Study of the Business of Federal Courts - Report on Criminal Cases, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 395)
    - Proposed rules governing practice and procedure in criminal cases, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 396)
    - Donovan report on Administration of Bankrupt Estates, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 397)
    - Bankruptcy study data
      - 1929 (Box 20, Folder 398)
      - 1929 (Box 21, Folder 399)
    - U.S. District Court, Southern District of New York - inquiry into bankruptcy abuses, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 400)
    - Bankruptcy research in British law, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 401)
    - Bankruptcy opinions, 1931-1935 (Box 21, Folder 402)
    - Bankruptcy Act amendment - memoranda by T.D. Thacher (Box 21, Folder 403)
    - Bankruptcy investigation - data on railroads (Box 21, Folder 404-405)
    - Bankruptcy forms (Box 21, Folder 406)
    - Bankruptcy - Supreme Court orders - correspondence and memoranda (Box 21, Folder 407)
    - Yale University Law School's bankruptcy investigation - correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 22, Folder 408)
    - Corporate reorganization - memoranda (Box 22, Folder 409)
    - Proposed changes in bankruptcy laws - memoranda and correspondence, 1932-1940 (Box 22, Folder 410)
    - Memorandum to Solicitor General on bankruptcy, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 411)
      - Annotations, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 412)
      - Appendix, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 413)
    - Bankruptcy legislation
      - House bills (Box 22, Folder 414)
      - House bills (Box 23, Folder 415)
      - Senate bills (Box 23, Folder 416-417)
    - Bankruptcy investigation - Clarence, Sutherland correspondence, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 418)
    - Bankruptcy bill
      - Minutes of Senate Hearings, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 419)
      - General revisions, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 420-421)
      - As passed, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 422-423)
    - Scrapbook - clippings, Solicitor General
      - 1930-1933 (Box 24, Folder 424)
      - 1931-1932 (Box 25, Folder 425)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 25, Folder 426)
  - Section B. New York City Politics and Charter Revision
    - Proposed charter and report of charter revision commission, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 427)
    - Charter data and memoranda, 1934 (Box 26, Folder 428)
    - Charter Code Board of Statutory Consolidation - correspondence and memoranda, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 429)
    - Charter Revision Commission - correspondence re: appropriations and expenditures, 1935-1937 (Box 26, Folder 430)
    - Charter suit - correspondence and memoranda, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 431-432)
    - New York City charter suit, Bowe v. Cohen memoranda and correspondence, 1937 (Box 27, Folder 433-435)
    - New York City charter suit, Mulville v. Cohen - memoranda, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 436)
    - New York City charter suit, Mooney v. Cohen - memoranda, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 437)
    - New York City charter, proportional representation issue - correspondence and memoranda (Box 28, Folder 438-439)
    - Charter Commission
      - General correspondence, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 440-442)
      - Vouchers (Box 28, Folder 443)
      - Vouchers (Box 29, Folder 444)
    - Charter referendum - memoranda, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 445)
    - Charter campaign victory - letters of congratulations, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 446-447)
    - Charter victory dinner - correspondence and program, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 448)
    - Charter - petition for amendment, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 449)
    - Charter Revision Commission - clippings scrapbook
      - Vol. I, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 450)
      - Vol. II, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 451)
      - Vol. III, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 452)
    - Fusion - memoranda and correspondence (Box 30, Folder 453)
    - Fusion leaders split with La Guardia - correspondence and clippings, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 454)
    - Functional chart, 1934-1935 (Box 30, Folder 455)
    - Home Rule Law, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 456)
    - Mayoralty campaign - correspondence and memoranda, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 457)
    - Official correspondence, 1944-1950 (Box 30, Folder 458)
    - Election fraud matter - correspondence and memoranda, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 459)
    - Planning Commission - correspondence and memoranda, 1937-1939, 1949-1950 (Box 30, Folder 460)
    - Pisciotta Case - correspondence and memoranda, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 461)
    - Hines Case - correspondence and memoranda, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 462)
    - Seabury's Pecora for Mayor statement - clippings and memoranda, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 463)
    - New York City Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report - correspondence, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 464)
    - Letters of congratulations on appointment as New York City Corporation Counsel, 1943 (Box 31, Folder 465)
  - Section C. New York State Court of Appeals
    - Congratulatory letters on appointment to New York Court of Appeals
      - 1943 May (Box 31, Folder 466-469)
      - 1943 May-June (Box 32, Folder 470)
    - Correspondence in support of 1943 Court of Appeals campaign, 1943 August-December (Box 32, Folder 471)
    - Correspondence on retirement from Court of Appeals, 1948 November-December (Box 32, Folder 472)
    - Criminal cases - motions for leave to appeal, 1946-1948, 1945-1946 (Box 32, Folder 473-474)
    - Lists of undecided cases, 1943-1948 (Box 32, Folder 475)
    - Cases not participating in, 1945-1946 (Box 32, Folder 476)
    - Decisions
      - 1944-1947 (Box 32, Folder 477-478)
      - 1948 (Box 33, Folder 479)
    - State of New York Judicial Council - correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 33, Folder 480)
    - Certificates of attorneys to practice in other states (Box 33, Folder 481)
    - New York State Board of Law Examiners - correspondence and reports, 1945-1948 (Box 33, Folder 482)
    - Votes on cases discussed in conference, 1943-1948 (Box 33, Folder 483)
    - Court of Appeals law clerks (Box 33, Folder 484)
    - Applicants for secretarial work (Box 33, Folder 485)
    - Court of Appeals memoranda, Misc. (Box 33, Folder 486)
    - Cases, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 487)
    - Cases, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 488-489)
    - Motions, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 490)
    - Cases, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 491-495)
    - Cases, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 496)
    - Motions, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 497-500)
    - Cases, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 501)
    - Cases, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 502-504)
    - Motions, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 505-507)
    - Cases, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 508-509)
    - Cases, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 510-511)
    - Motions, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 512-514)
    - Cases, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 515-516)
    - Cases, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 517)
    - Motions, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 518-519)
    - Cases, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 520-521)
    - Motions, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 522-523)
    - Congratulatory letters on return to Simpson, Thacher & Bartlett, 1949 January-March (Box 39, Folder 524)
  - Section D. Legal Associations
    - American Bar Association
      - General correspondence, 1930-1940 (Box 39, Folder 525)
      - House of Delegates - correspondence and memoranda, 1940-1943 (Box 39, Folder 526)
      - Special Committee on Supreme Court Proposals - correspondence and memoranda, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 527)
      - Section on Criminal Law - correspondence, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 528)
    - American Judicature Society - correspondence, 1930-1940 (Box 39, Folder 529)
    - Bar of Supreme Court: memorial resolutions for Sutherland, McReynolds, Hughes, Murphy and Stone, 1944-1950 (Box 40, Folder 530)
    - Lawyers Committee of USO Campaign - correspondence, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 531)
    - New York City Bar Association
      - General correspondence, 1932-1934, 1935-1937, 1938-1940 (Box 40, Folder 532-534)
      - Arbitration cases, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 535)
      - Annual statements of President Thacher, 1934, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 536)
      - Committee on Administrative Law correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 40, Folder 537)
      - Committee on Federal Judiciary Re-organization
        - Correspondence and memoranda, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 538)
        - Clippings, notes and memoranda, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 539)
        - General information: speeches, bills, articles, etc., 1936-1937 (Box 40, Folder 540)
        - General information: speeches, bills, articles, etc., 1937 (Box 41, Folder 541)
      - Committee on Practice and Procedure in State Supreme Court - minutes, 1922, 1923 (Box 41, Folder 542)
      - Judiciary Committee - correspondence, 1933-1937, 1937, 1937, 1938-1940, 1940-1941 (Box 41, Folder 543-547)
      - Special Committee on Supreme Court Proposals
        - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 548)
        - Research notes and memoranda, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 549)
      - Special Committee Sub-committee - correspondence, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 550)
      - Tax exemptions, 1933-1937 (Box 42, Folder 551)
      - War Committee - correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 42, Folder 552)
    - New York County Lawyers Association
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1936-1942 (Box 42, Folder 553)
      - Judiciary Committee - correspondence and memoranda, 1938-1942 (Box 42, Folder 554)
      - National Defense Committee - correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 42, Folder 555)
      - Supreme Court Committee - correspondence and memoranda, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 556)
    - New York Patent Law Association - correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 42, Folder 557)
    - New York State Bar Association
      - Correspondence, 1934-1950 (Box 42, Folder 558)
      - Committee on Municipal Law - correspondence, 1938-1942 (Box 43, Folder 559)
      - Committee on Municipal Law - reports (Box 43, Folder 560)
      - Committee on Nominations - correspondence, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 561)
      - Committee on Selection of Judges - correspondence, 1936-1942 (Box 43, Folder 562)
  - Section E. Institutions Which Thacher Served as Trustee or Director
    - American Law Institute
      - Correspondence, 1927-1943, 1944-1950 (Box 43, Folder 563-564)
      - Council minutes, 1946, 1947-1948, 1949-1950 (Box 43, Folder 565-567)
      - Draft reports (Box 44, Folder 568-569)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - correspondence, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 570)
    - Commonwealth Fund
      - Correspondence, 1942-1943, 1944-1945, 1946-1948, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 571-574)
      - Board of Directors minutes, 1942-1943, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 575-576)
    - Foreign Bondholders Protective Council Inc.
      - Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 44, Folder 577)
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1945-1950 (Box 45, Folder 578)
    - New York Public Library
      - Correspondence, 1934-1937, 1938, 1939-1943 (Box 45, Folder 579-581)
      - Pensions (Box 45, Folder 582)
      - Reports and memoranda (Box 45, Folder 583-584)
      - Reports and memoranda (Box 46, Folder 585)
    - Taft School
      - Correspondence, 1928-1933, 1934-1935, 1936-1937, 1938-1942, 1943-1948 (Box 46, Folder 586-590)
      - Corporation reports (Box 46, Folder 591-592)
      - Publicity materials (Box 47, Folder 593)
      - Alumni Association and Fund (Box 47, Folder 594)
      - Trustee meeting minutes (Box 47, Folder 595)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association - correspondence, 1938-1943 (Box 47, Folder 596)
    - Yale Corporation
      - Committee on Honorary Degrees, correspondence and memoranda, 1930-1942, 1947-1948, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 597-599)
      - Joint Committee on New Haven Hospital, 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 600)
    - Yale University
      - Alumni Association correspondence and publications, 1933-1950 (Box 48, Folder 601)
      - Branford College correspondence, 1932-1950 (Box 48, Folder 602)
      - Class of 1904 correspondence and memorabilia, 1927-1939, 1940-1950 (Box 48, Folder 603-604)
      - Golf Courses, Ray Thompkins Memorial, 1924-1926 (Box 48, Folder 605)
      - Law School - Class of 1907 (Box 48, Folder 606)
      - Law School - correspondence and memoranda, 1930-1939, 1940-1941, 1945-1948, 1949 Jan, 1949 February - 1950 (Box 49, Folder 607-611)
      - Medical School, Institute of Nutrition, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 612)
      - Mory's, Award of Cup to Thacher, 1940 May 29 (Box 49, Folder 613)
      - Reorganization of Alumni Board and executive powers, 1947-1949 (Box 49, Folder 614)
      - Francis White, 1942 June - July (Box 50, Folder 615)
      - General correspondence and memoranda, 1927-1933, 1934-1941, 1943-1948, 1949-1950 (Box 50, Folder 616-619)
      - Miscellaneous documents (Box 50, Folder 620)
  - Section F. Clubs, Societies, Service organizations
    - Thacher's club memberships (list) (Box 50, Folder 621)
    - Bill of Rights Commemorative Society - correspondence, charter, minutes, 1943-1945 (Box 50, Folder 622)
    - Children's Court Conference - correspondence, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 623)
    - Reppy Sponsoring Committee - correspondence, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 624)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. - correspondence, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 625)
    - Dome Lake Club - correspondence, 1927-1941 (Box 50, Folder 626-627)
    - Institute of Criminal Science - correspondence, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 628)
    - Kedgwick Fishing Club - correspondence, 1940-1943 (Box 51, Folder 629-630)
    - Legal Aid Society (Box 51, Folder 631)
    - Links Club - correspondence, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 632)
    - Military Training Camps Association - correspondence and publicity pamphlets, 1940-1942 (Box 51, Folder 633)
    - Misquamicut Golf Club - correspondence, 1925-1933, 1934-1939, 1941-1942, 1943-1948 (Box 51, Folder 634-637)
    - Morgan Library - correspondence, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 638)
    - National Conference of Jews and Christians - correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box 52, Folder 639)
    - National Economic League - correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 52, Folder 640)
    - National Fund for Medical Education - correspondence, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 641)
    - National Legal Aid Association - correspondence, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 642)
    - National Republican Club - correspondence, 1933-1942 (Box 52, Folder 643)
    - New England Society
      - Correspondence, 1929-1940 (Box 52, Folder 644)
      - Committee on Financial Condition, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 645)
      - Correspondence and annual reports, 1941-1943, 1941-1948 (Box 52, Folder 646-647)
      - Annual dinner, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 648)
    - New York City, Hospital Council of - correspondence and report by T.D.T on use of tax funds to care for indigent sick., 1940-1943 (Box 53, Folder 649)
    - New York City, United Hospital Fund of - correspondence, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 650)
    - New York Hospital, Society of correspondence, 1943 (Box 53, Folder 651)
    - New York Law Institute - correspondence and annual reports, 1935-1940 (Box 53, Folder 652)
    - New York State Museum - correspondence, 1929-1931 (Box 53, Folder 653)
    - New York State Conference on Legal Education - correspondence and reports, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 654)
    - Phillips Academy, Andover - correspondence, 1932-1940, 1941-1944 (Box 53, Folder 655-656)
    - Practising Law Institute - correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 657)
    - Quinnipiack Club - correspondence, 1934-1938 (Box 53, Folder 658)
    - Research Council on the Problems of Alcohol
      - Correspondence, 1938-1945 (Box 53, Folder 659-660)
      - Publicity materials (Box 53, Folder 661)
      - Publicity materials (Box 54, Folder 662)
    - Thacher School - correspondence and memorabilia, 1938-1940 (Box 54, Folder 663-664)
    - Union Club - correspondence and committee reports, 1933-1936, 1937-1939, 1940-1942, 1943-1946 (Box 54, Folder 665-668)
    - United China Relief - correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 55, Folder 669)
    - University Club - correspondence, 1925-1935, 1936-1940, 1941-1949 (Box 55, Folder 670-672)
    - Watch Hill Beach Club - correspondence, 1936-1941 (Box 55, Folder 673)
    - World's Fair (1939) - lawyers luncheon - correspondence, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 674)
    - World's Fair - correspondence and annual reports, 1939-1940 (Box 55, Folder 675-676)
    - Yale Club of New York - correspondence, 1925-1942 (Box 55, Folder 677)
    - Yeamans Hall Club - correspondence, 1928-1947 (Box 55, Folder 678)
    - Club dues, 1944, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 679)
  - Section G. Miscellaneous Subject Files
    - Borah, William E.
      - Speeches, 1934-1937 (Box 56, Folder 680)
      - Clippings, 1934-1940 (Box 56, Folder 681)
    - Bridges Bill and sale of destroyers to England, 1940-1941 (Box 56, Folder 682)
    - Capshaw, Hulon - investigation, 1939-1940 (Box 56, Folder 683-684)
    - Columbia Law School, Harlan Fiske Stone Moot Court Competition, 1948 April 30 (Box 56, Folder 685)
    - Dewey Committee on Court's Treatment of Minors, 1941-1942, 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 686-687)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., clippings, 1943-1950 (Box 57, Folder 688)
    - Dumbarton Oaks Conference re: International Court of Justice, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 689)
    - Ellis Island Committee
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1933-1934 (Box 57, Folder 690)
      - Research and reports, 1933-1934 (Box 57, Folder 691)
      - Committee Report, 1934 March (Box 57, Folder 692)
    - Expulsion of the New York Socialist assemblymen - correspondence and memoranda, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 693)
    - Expulsion of the New York State Socialist assemblymen - correspondence and memoranda, 1920 (Box 57, Folder 694)
    - Fox, William re: Executive Pardon, 1941-1945 (Box 57, Folder 695)
    - Frankfurter, Felix
      - Skit, 1941 April 5 (Box 58, Folder 696)
      - Speech by and articles about (Box 58, Folder 697)
      - Clippings, 1934-1941 (Box 58, Folder 698)
    - Gambling: municipal lottery, etc., 1934-1940 (Box 58, Folder 699)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K., writings, gifts, etc. (Box 58, Folder 700)
    - Gumberg, Alex
      - Russian-American Trade Relations, 1919-1939 (Box 58, Folder 701)
      - Correspondence, clippings, etc., 1919-1939 (Box 58, Folder 702)
    - Hauptmann Trial, controversy with Watson of Law Journal, 1935 January - March (Box 58, Folder 703)
    - History of "Simpson, Thacher and Bartlett" (Box 58, Folder 704)
    - Honest Ballot Association Election Committee, 1940 (Box 58, Folder 705)
    - Judge Learned Hand bust presentation - correspondence, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 706)
    - Judges' salaries (Holmes' pension), 1930-1934 (Box 58, Folder 707)
    - Judges' salaries: Desmond Act, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 708)
    - Kenyon, Dorothy appearance before Senate Committee, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 709)
    - Knight, Richard A., case of, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 710)
    - Labor Act - clippings, articles, etc., 1941 (Box 59, Folder 711)
    - Manton Case - clippings, correspondence, memoranda, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 712)
    - Morgan and Cie (Paris) - correspondence, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 713)
    - Martin, Judge George W.: removal proceedings against, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 714)
    - Medina, Harold R. - tribute dinner proposed by Common Cause, 1950 (Box 59, Folder 715)
    - Neutrality and Embargo Laws, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 716)
    - New York Constitutional Convention Committee: sub-committee on taxation and finance - correspondence and memoranda, 1937 July-1938 Jan, 1938 February-July (Box 59, Folder 717-718)
    - Parker, John J. - Supreme Court nomination - correspondence and memoranda, 1930 (Box 59, Folder 719)
    - Pound, Justice Cuthbert W. - presentation of portrait to Court of Appeals, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 720)
    - Radio-Keith-Orpheum Corp. re: organization proceedings, 1935 (Box 60, Folder 721)
    - Railroad Corporate reorganization
      - Memoranda and correspondence, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 722)
      - Memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 723)
    - Recommendations
      - For Bar Association (Box 60, Folder 724)
      - For military service, 1941-1943 (Box 60, Folder 725)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 726)
    - Robins, Col. Raymond - clippings, 1932-1933 (Box 60, Folder 727)
    - Roosevelt, F.D. - third term, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 728)
    - Silver Oar presentation to U.S. District Court - correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 729)
    - Supreme Court reorganization - memoranda, correspondence, bills, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 730-731)
    - Taft Memorial - correspondence, 1930-1931 (Box 60, Folder 732)
    - U.N. Genocide Convention: correspondence and memorandum, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 733)
    - U.S. Board of Tax Appeals: correspondence concerning permission to practice before 1936-1938 (Box 61, Folder 734)
    - U.S. Supreme Court
      - Cornerstone laying: correspondence and memoranda, 1932 October 13 (Box 61, Folder 735)
      - "Since Frankie Spanked the Court" and "W.O. Douglas Dialogue" (spoofs), 1939 June 10 (Box 61, Folder 736)
      - Miscellaneous articles, correspondence, etc., 1930-1940 (Box 61, Folder 737)
      - Proposals - miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 738)
    - Vanderberg Tariff Opinion - correspondence and memoranda, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 739)
    - Thacher, John S. - correspondence with and concerning (Box 61, Folder 740)
    - Watch Hill Fire District: Charter - correspondence and memoranda, 1939-1940 (Box 61, Folder 741)
    - Watch Hill Power Station Suit
      - Correspondence and memoranda, 1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 742)
      - Court decisions and information, 1941-1942 (Box 61, Folder 743)
    - Wingo, Otis T. "Powers of President Roosevelt under the Unlimited Emergency", 1941 May 30 (Box 61, Folder 744)
- Speeches, 1925-1949; Series III; 2.25 linear feet (5 boxes)
  Speeches are arranged chronologically. Folder captions not in quotes indicate the general subject content of the speech.
  - Federal Lawyers Luncheon [?], 1925 February [?] (Box 62, Folder 745)
  - Yale Law School, 1927 (Box 62, Folder 746)
  - Taft School, 1928 April 13 (Box 62, Folder 747)
  - Notes for speeches on Bankruptcy Act, Undated [after 1930] (Box 62, Folder 748)
  - Introduction to Washington, D.C. Yale Club, 1930 May 8 (Box 62, Folder 749)
  - Changes and problems at Yale Law School, 1930 June 16 (Box 62, Folder 750)
  - Reform and the legal profession, 1930 July 11 (Box 62, Folder 751)
  - Introduction for Col. J. Miller Kenyon, 1930 August [?] (Box 62, Folder 752)
  - "The National Bankruptcy Act", 1930 August 21 (Box 62, Folder 753)
  - Material for speeches on Bankruptcy, 1931-1933 (Box 62, Folder 754)
  - Bankruptcy Act, 1931, February 26 (Box 62, Folder 755)
  - "Genesis and Present Duties of Office of Solicitor General", 1931 May 9 (Box 62, Folder 756)
  - Exercise of judiciary power, 1932 January 23 (Box 62, Folder 757)
  - Holmes' 91st birthday celebration, 1932 May 8 (Box 62, Folder 758)
  - Bankruptcy Act, 1932 March 18, 1932 June 3 (Box 62, Folder 759-760)
  - Against F.D.R.: economic issues in campaign, 1932 September 10 (Box 62, Folder 761)
  - Justice, law and crime, 1932 November 25 (Box 62, Folder 762)
  - Notes for speech on "Fusion" ticket, [1933?] (Box 62, Folder 763)
  - In favor of Fusion ticket, 1933 October 10 (Box 62, Folder 764)
  - "Fusion" ticket, 1933 October 18 (Box 62, Folder 765)
  - Endorsement of "Fusion" ticket, 1933 October 20 (Box 62, Folder 766)
  - Endorsements of "Fusion" - non-partisan ticket for NYC, 1933 November 2 (Box 62, Folder 767)
  - First Bar Association dinner for new judges, 1933 November 27 (Box 62, Folder 768)
  - Charter revision, Undated [after 1934] (Box 62, Folder 769)
  - "Public Relations of the Legal Profession", 1934 January 19 (Box 62, Folder 770)
  - Legal profession and the public, 1934 March 14 (Box 62, Folder 771)
  - "The Business of the Supreme Court" notes, 1934 April 17 (Box 62, Folder 772)
  - Coping with Crime: Fighting the Gangster and the Racketeer, 1934 May 5 (Box 62, Folder 773)
  - "National Recovery and the Supremacy of Law", 1934 May 9 (Box 62, Folder 774)
  - Reform of N.R.A., 1934 July 30 (Box 63, Folder 775)